http://ashleycountyledger.com/site/privacy.html

Hamburg, AR
(71646)
Today
Clear to partly cloudy. Low near 50F. Winds light and variable..
Tonight
Clear to partly cloudy. Low near 50F. Winds light and variable.
Read more
This privacy notice discloses privacy practices for www.ashleycountyledger.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:— What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it is shared.— What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.—The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.—How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside Ashley County Publishing Co., Inc., other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. place an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about subscription specials, new products or services, or changes to this policy.You may opt out of any future contacts at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email at: the_ledger@att.net or 870-853-2424:—See what data we have about you, if any.—Change/correct any data we have about you.—Have us delete any data we have about you.—Express any concern you have about our use of your data. Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Whenever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are given access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact the Business Office immediately via telephone at 870-853-2424 or email the publisher at the_ledger@att.net. Registration In order to use portions of this website, a user must complete a subscription form. This subscription form requires certain information (such as name, address, telephone and email address). This information is used to contact you about services/products on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender and age) about yourself, but it is not required. Orders We request information when orders are placed in several locations on our site (such as subscription, classified ads, etc.). To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and home address) and financial information (like credit card, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use the information to contact you. Cookies We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access and identify repeat visitors to our site. For example, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.Some of our business partners (for example: advertisers) may use cookies on our site. However, we have no access or control over these cookies. Sharing We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.We may use an outside shipping company to mail photos and other products, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.We sometimes partner with outside parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. Links Our website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. Surveys & Contests Occasionally, our site requests information via surveys, contests or for news items. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose your information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and home address) and demographic information (such as zip code, age, etc.). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. News items will be used for editorial news content that may be published in the printed Ashley County Ledger. As described above, we and third parties may use cookies and other tracking technologies to facilitate serving relevant ads to you. For example, these technologies help us determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before, tailor ads to you if you have visited our site before, and avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. You can learn more about certain types of targeted advertising by visiting http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/ where you may also opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from participating ad networks, audience segment providers, ad serving vendors, and other service providers.
Sign Up for Our Newsletters
Success! An email has been sent to
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
Current Headlines
News updates hitting your inbox.
© Copyright 2020 Ashley County Ledger, PO Box 471 Hamburg, AR | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
